Marching to the New Wonderland
The Energy Seed
Thunderbolt!
Morning Sun!
Lightning Angel!
Hurricane!
Rainbow!
Let’s go!
I wish these trains were real.
We could be heroes of the world!
How could you possibly be “heroes”
when you’re this careless with insects?
Come on out, Sirius!
Don’t worry, Wolnie.
With my newest invention, Sirius, at your service,
no one will dare to harm you.
This is bad.
I’ve got yet another wrinkle in the corner of my eye.
Wolnie, I can get you the moon and the stars,
but I can’t do anything about wrinkles.
I don’t care! I want to look young!
Aha!
What is it?
There’s this magical “Energy Seed”,
a source of unlimited vital energy.
If we get it,
you’d stay young forever, and I’d have unlimited power!
Well? Go find it.
I can’t.
This type of seed is extremely small. We won’t find it.
You know what? I’ve made a transformation gun.
I’d have a better time searching if I’m shrunken down.
Then hurry up.
Don’t be long, Wolffy!
Wolnie,
just you wait!
I’ll give you a hand.
Thanks, Wolnie!
Don’t be long.
It’s a big train!
Wilie?
The big train’s inside is just like our house!
This is your dad’s stuff. Don’t touch anything.
He’s awake.
What is he saying?
He says
his “Energy Seed” is missing,
and he must find it right away.
Huh?
“Energy Seed”?
I guess being so small isn’t all that convenient.
It’s not over here, Mr. Slowy.
It’s not over here, either.
Keep searching.
Yes, sir.
I found it!
Great.
The goats have the Energy Seed?
Getting it will be a piece of cake.
This is the Energy Seed, huh?
It looks just like a gem.
How tiny.
Wolffy!
Hand over the Energy Seed!
No way!
In that case,
Sirius!
What… What is…?
This is my newly invented tank train,
“Sirius”.
Hand over the Energy Seed!
Good thing I’ve transformed our toy trains into tanks, too.
Really, Mr. Slowy?
Yes. Let’s summon them together.
Yes, sir!
Daybreak!
Rainbow!
Lightning Angel!
Hurricane!
Morning Sun!
Come on out, Thunderbolt!
What do you think of our Magic Trains, Wolffy?
I’ll make you guys shrink.
We’ll see just how well your Magic Trains fare.
Well, you’re quick.
Oh no, my train doesn’t have any defense!
Rainbow Shield!
You blocked it?
Now’s my chance.
I’ll deliver the last hit.
Sparky, your train is a mechanic train.
It’s not for attacking.
What? No!
Now’s my chance.
The Magic Trains are no match for me.
Uh-oh.
What is this place?
The plants here are huge.
Grandpa Beetle, how did you grow?
I didn’t grow. You guys shrunk.
Huh?
Shrunk?
We really did shrink.
What now?
I’ll miss out on so many foods if I’m this small.
Don’t worry,
I have a spray to make us grow back.
We can return whenever we’d like to.
Yay!
You can’t go.
Grandpa Beetle, we still have to go home and do homework today.
We have to go home and eat, too.
Professor Beetle, we’ve already found the Energy Seed for you,
so we’ll be on our way.
But you guys are the only hope for saving the Big Tree World!
Saving the world?
Yes. The Energy Seed is the Sun’s life essence.
My job is to collect these essences
and deliver them to the Big Tree’s Summit.
If I can’t deliver the Energy Seed to the Summit
within three months,
the Big Tree World will wither and all of its insects will go extinct.
But now, I’m old and not as fast as I used to be.
I might not be able to make it on time.
Grandpa Beetle, we’ll go save the Big Tree World, then.
Right, we have to do something.
Well,
traveling the world also counts as education.
Professor Beetle,
you can leave this great mission to us.
The Big Tree World’s entrance is up ahead.
We’ll need to deliver the Energy Seed to the Big Tree’s Summit
as soon as possible.
We’re just climbing the tree, right? That’s easy.
Are trees actually this huge?
Through the eyes of insects, the world is, in fact, this big.
So how long will it take us to get the seed up there?
Wouldn’t transforming back to normal make it easier?
You can’t do that.
Delivering the seed is a tradition.
It must be done from the perspective of the insects,
nothing else.
The Energy Seed is mine now!
Mr. Slowy, what now?
Don’t worry. Watch this.
Magic Trains, assemble!
Assemble?
Follow me, kids.
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
We look awesome while assembled!
We can do more things, too.
We also have more power.
We’re also faster than before.
Watch this!
Guess who?
Son?
What are you doing here?
I should be asking YOU that.
Wolnie?
I came onto the train to find Wilie,
and the next thing I know, the train’s flown off to here.
You better take us home right now!
Goodbye, Mr. Wolffy!
You’re not going anywhere.
Wolnie, I’ve located the Energy Seed,
the one that promises eternal youth.
It’s with the goats.
Great! Let’s get them!
Off we go!
Yay! We’re going out!
END